MacKaye Family papers ML-5
Rauner Special Collections Library
- Percy MacKaye, 1870-1945, 1954, 1975; 16
  - Box: 54, 1896-1928 (Box 54)
    - Play: Partial MS The Canterbury Pilgrims, 1902 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Play: Typescript The Canterbury Tales Act I, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Play: Typescript The Canterbury Tales Act II, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Play: Typescript The Canterbury Tales Act III, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Play: Typescript The Canterbury Tales Act IV, 1903 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Masque: MS Chuck, 1909 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Play: MS Dark o' the Moon, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Masque: Typescript The Evergreen Tree, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Masque: MS The Evergreen Tree, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Pageant: MS Eeny Meeny, 1912 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Box: 55, 1905-1924 (Box 55)
    Box: 55
    - Play: MS Ferris the Wolf, 1905 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Masque: MS Foxfire Tale, 1928 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Play: MS The Funeralizing of Chick-neck, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Play: MS A Garland For Sylvia, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Play: Typescript A Garland For Sylvia, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Play: MS Gettysburg, 1907 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Play: MS The Gobbler of God, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Play: Typescript Half Hour Happenings of the Teeles Family, 1911 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Play: The Emigrants/The immigrants, 1913 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Play: MS Ingomar, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Masque: Typescript & MS Interludes, undated (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Play: Typescript Jeanne D'Arc, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Play: Typescript Jeanne D'Arc Act I - V, undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Play: MS Jeanne D'Arc, 1905 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Play: Typescript Jeanne D'Arc (partial), undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Box: 56, 1894-1922 (Box 56)
    Box: 56
    - Play: Typescript and MS The Life Mask, 1904 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Play: Typescript Mashallah, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Play: Typescript and partial MS Mater, 1905 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Play MS Napoleon Crossing the Rockies, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Play: MS Nereida, 1904 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Play: MS One Way To Get Shut Of A Wife, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Play: MS Ornis, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Ephemeral Items and Newspaper Clippings on Pageantry, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Masque: The Pay-Master, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Play: Typescript Pride and Prejudice, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Pantomime: Typescript The Prince and Pierrot, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Play: MS Rip Van Winkle, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Masque: MS The Roll Call, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Masque: Typescript The Sainted Cow, 1894 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Pageant and Masque Ephemeral Items, Bulletin and MS St. Louis, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Masque: Typescript and MS Sanctuary, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Masque: Ephemeral Items and Correspondence Sanctuary, 1913-1914 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Masque: Typescript Bound Sappho and Phaon, 1906 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Masque: Typescript Sappho and Phaon, 1906 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Box: 57, 1906-1928 (Box 57)
    Box: 57
    - Masque: MS Sappho And Phaon, 1906 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Masque: MS Sappho And Phaon, 1907 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Masque: Typescript Sappho And Phaon, 1907 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Masque: Typescript "Dramatis Personae" individual script excerpts, 1907 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Masque: Typescript "Dramatis Personae" individual script excerpts and Rehearsal Notes, 1907 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Play: Printed pages The Scarecrow Act I - IV, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Play: Typescript The Scarecrow Act I - IV, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Play: Typescript The Scarecrow (Die Vogelscheuche) German Translation, 1907 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Play: MS The Seven Sagamores, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Play: MS The Sibyl, 1912 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Masque: Shakespeare Masque, undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Play: Typescript Sinbad The Sailor, 1917 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Play: Typescript A Song At The Castle, undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Play: MS The Sphynx, 1913 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Play: Typescript A Stained Glass Window, undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Play: MS The Skippers Of Nancy Gloucester, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Play: Typescript and Preface This Fine-Pretty World, 1923 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Play: Correspondence and Ephemera This Fine-Pretty World, 1923-1924 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Box: 58, 1907-1924 (Box 58)
    Box: 58
    - Play: Correspondence and Ephemera This Fine-Pretty World, 1923-1924 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Play: MS The Thoroughbred, 1910 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Play: Typescript The Thoroughbred, 1911 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Play: MS A Thousand Years Ago, 1913 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Play: MS Timber, 1923 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Play: MS Wachusett, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Play: Typescript Washington, 1919 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Play: MS with cover Washington, 1919 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Play: MS Who All's Black Hat, 1929 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Play: Typescript and MS Preface Yankee Fantasies, 1911 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Galley Proofs: Anti-Matrimony, 1910 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Galley Proofs: Ferris The Wolf, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Galley Proofs: A Dozen Prompt Notes, 1909 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Galley Proofs and Typescript: A Garden To Sylvia, undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Galley Proofs: Gobbler Of God, 1924 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Galley Proofs: Lincoln Centenary Ode, undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Galley Proofs: Mountain Fantasies, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Galley Proofs: Ninety-Seven, 1907 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Play: MS The Nun's Priest's Tale, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Box: 59, 1907-1932 (Box 59)
    Box: 59
    - Galley Proofs: Paul Kauvar or Anarchy, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Galley Proofs: Pride and Prejudice, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Play: MS Rita, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Play: Typescript Rita, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Galley Proofs: Sappho And Phaon, 1907 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Galley Proofs: Wakefield, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Galley Proofs: Wakefield, 1932 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Galley Proofs: The Scarecrow, 1908 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Play: MS and Typescript Preface The Scarecrow, 1908 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Essay: Typescript The Playhouse And The Play, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Play: Printed partial copy of The Scarecrow, 1908 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Page Proofs: The Scarecrow, 1908 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Page Proofs: Jeanne D'Arc, 1906 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Page Proofs and partial typescript: Mater, 1908 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Page Proofs: The Present Hour - A Book of Poems, 1914 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Page Proofs: Sanctuary, 1913 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Page Proofs: Tomorrow, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Box: 60, undated (Box 60)
    Box: 60
    - Plays and Poems: Miscellaneous Proofs, Typescripts and Manuscripts, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Plays and Poems: Miscellaneous Proofs and Typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Book: Partial Page Proofs The Civic Theatre, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Poems: Page Proofs, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Contains notebooks of poetry and other writings, 1899-1910 (Box 61)
    Contains notebooks of poetry and other writings
  - Notebooks Containing Play Manuscripts, Entomolgy Studies, and Schoolwork as well as Diaries, Tel..., 1860-1942 (Box 62)
    Notebooks Containing Play Manuscripts, Entomolgy Studies, and Schoolwork as well as Diaries, Telegrams and Clippings
  - Box: 63, 1860-1955 (Box 63)
    Box: 63
    - Epoch: Typed list of names of prominent people mentioned, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Epoch: Newspaper and Journal Reviews, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Press Clippings about other works, 1920's - 1930's (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Press Clippings, Reviews of Plays, 1860-1918 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Press Clippings, Reviews, 1920's - 1930's (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Epoch: Publicity Materials, 1920's (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Press Clippings, 1871-1873 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Schweizer Amerikanische Zeitung [Swiss American Newspaper], 1955-05 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Steele MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Mary Medbery MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Sarah Stetson Pevear (Aunt Sadie), undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Marion Morse MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Harold Steele MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: William Payson MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: James Medbery MacKaye, undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Engraving (possible stage design) and Play posters, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Box: 64, 1880's-1920's (Box 64)
    Box: 64
    - Photographs: Arthur Loring MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Arvia MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Hazel MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Benton MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Christy MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Robert Keith MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Buildings associated with the MacKaye Family, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Photographs of signature card of five or six generations of MacKayes, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Kentucky Mountain Photos by Ewing Galloway, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Civil War Encampment possibly with Steele MacKaye, undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Other Family Members, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Portrait Album and Deguerrotype, undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Photographs: Celluloid Negatives, undated (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Photographs: Glass Negatives (some very brittle), undated (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous, rolled up, undated (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1950-05 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Box: 65, 1880-1920's (Box 65)
    Box: 65
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Friends and Ephemera, circa1870's-1920's (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Friends and Ephemera, circa1870's-1920's (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Masque Performers and Stages, sketches, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and Ephemera: Masque Saint Louis, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Photographs and Ephemera: Masque Caliban, 1916 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Rip Van Winkle, 1919 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Masque Sanctuary - A Bird Masque, 1913 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Dry-Mounted Production Stills, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Miscellaneous Dry- Mounted Production Stills, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Contains Dry-Mounted Theatrical Stills, 1880-1920's (Box 66)
    Contains Dry-Mounted Theatrical Stills
  - Contains Scrapbook: Anti-Matrimony, 1910 (Box 67)
    Contains Scrapbook: Anti-Matrimony
  - Contains Scrapbook: Biographical, Friends, Book Reviews, 1906-1907 (Box 68)
    Contains Scrapbook: Biographical, Friends, Book Reviews
  - Contains Scrapbook: Biographical, Friends, Book Reviews, 1911 (Box 69)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Caliban, Boston, 1916 (Box 70)
    Contains Scrapbook: Caliban, Boston
  - Contains Scrapbook: Caliban II, 1916 (Box 71)
    Contains Scrapbook: Caliban II
  - Contains Scrapbook: Caliban III, 1916 (Box 72)
    Contains Scrapbook: Caliban III
  - Contains Scrapbook: Caliban Advertisments, 1916 (Box 73)
    Contains Scrapbook: Caliban Advertisments
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Pilgrims, 1903 (Box 74)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Pilgrims
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Pilgrims etc., 1903 (Box 75)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Pilgrims etc.
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Tales, Opera, 1903 (Box 76)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Canterbury Tales, Opera
  - Contains Scrapbook: Civic Drama Association, 1916 (Box 77)
    Contains Scrapbook: Civic Drama Association
  - Contains Scrapbook: Civic Movement and Politics, 1909-1916 (Box 78)
    Contains Scrapbook: Civic Movement and Politics
  - Contains Scrapbook: Dramatic Movement, 1906-1911 (Box 79)
    Contains Scrapbook: Dramatic Movement
  - Contains Scrapbook: Dramatic Movement, 1907-1915 (Box 80)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Dramatic Movement, 1912-1915 (Box 81)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Dramatic Movement, 1915 (Box 82)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Epoch, 1927 (Box 83)
    Contains Scrapbook: Epoch
  - Contains Scrapbook: Epoch I, 1927 (Box 84)
    Contains Scrapbook: Epoch I
  - Contains Scrapbook: Epoch Letters, A-P, 1927 (Box 85)
    Contains Scrapbook: Epoch Letters, A-P
  - Contains Scrapbook: Epoch Letters Q-W, 1927 (Box 86)
    Contains Scrapbook: Epoch Letters Q-W
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Evergreen Tree, undated (Box 87)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Evergreen Tree
  - Contains Scrapbook: Family, 1896-1913 (Box 88)
    Contains Scrapbook: Family
  - Contains Scrapbook: Family, 1904 (Box 89)
  - Contains Scrapbook: This Fine-Pretty World, 1923 (Box 90)
    Contains Scrapbook: This Fine-Pretty World
  - Contains Scrapbook: Friends, undated (Box 91)
    Contains Scrapbook: Friends
  - Contains Scrapbook: A Garland For Sylvia, undated (Box 92)
    Contains Scrapbook: A Garland For Sylvia
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Gobbler of God, 1927-1928 (Box 93)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Gobbler of God
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Immigrant, undated (Box 94)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Immigrant
  - Contains Scrapbook: Invitations and Souvenirs, 1875-1908 (Box 95)
    Contains Scrapbook: Invitations and Souvenirs
  - Contains Scrapbook: Invitations and Souvenirs, 1906-1911 (Box 96)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Jeanne d'Arc, 1906-1908 (Box 97)
    Contains Scrapbook: Jeanne d'Arc
  - Contains Scrapbook: Jeanne d'Arc, 1906-1916 (Box 98)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Jeanne d'Arc, 1907-1923 (Box 99)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Lectures, Drama of Democracy, Playhouse and Play, 1907-1908 (Box 100)
    Contains Scrapbook: Lectures, Drama of Democracy, Playhouse and Play
  - Contains Scrapbook: Mater, 1908 (Box 101)
    Contains Scrapbook: Mater
  - Contains Scrapbook: Miami Fellowship, undated (Box 102)
    Contains Scrapbook: Miami Fellowship
  - Contains Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Non-Theatrical, undated (Box 103)
    Contains Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Non-Theatrical
  - Contains Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Theatrical, 1904-1910 (Box 104)
    Contains Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Theatrical
  - Contains Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Theatrical, 1909-1913 (Box 105)
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Modern Reader's Chaucer, undated (Box 106)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Modern Reader's Chaucer
  - Contains Scrapbook: Natural Opera, undated (Box 107)
    Contains Scrapbook: Natural Opera
  - Contains Scrapbook: The New Citizenship, undated (Box 108)
    Contains Scrapbook: The New Citizenship
  - Contains Scrapbook: Pageants, 1895-1915 (Box 109)
    Contains Scrapbook: Pageants
  - Contains Scrapbook: Pageants, 1916 (Box 110)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Pageants and Festivals, undated (Box 111)
    Contains Scrapbook: Pageants and Festivals
  - Contains Scrapbook: Personal, 1898-1910 (Box 112)
    Contains Scrapbook: Personal
  - Contains Scrapbook: Personal, 1910-1913 (Box 113)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Personal, 1913-1920 (Box 114)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Personal, 1920-1924 (Box 115)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Personal, 1925-1928 (Box 116)
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Pilgrim and The Book, undated (Box 117)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Pilgrim and The Book
  - Contains Scrapbook: Play Readers and Amateur Performances, 1912-1913 (Box 118)
    Contains Scrapbook: Play Readers and Amateur Performances
  - Contains Scrapbook: Play Readers and Amateur Performance, 1913 (Box 119)
    Contains Scrapbook: Play Readers and Amateur Performance
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Playhouse and The Play, undated (Box 120)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Playhouse and The Play
  - Contains Scrapbook: Poems, 1909-1915 (Box 121)
    Contains Scrapbook: Poems
  - Contains Scrapbook: Poems II, 1915 (Box 122)
    Contains Scrapbook: Poems II
  - Contains Scrapbook: Poetry, 1910 (Box 123)
    Contains Scrapbook: Poetry
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Present Hour, 1914-1916 (Box 124)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Present Hour
  - Contains Scrapbook: Rip Van Winkle, 1919 (Box 125)
    Contains Scrapbook: Rip Van Winkle
  - Contains Scrapbook: Roll Call, 1918 (Box 126)
    Contains Scrapbook: Roll Call
  - Contains Scrapbook: Saint Louis and Pageants, undated (Box 127)
    Contains Scrapbook: Saint Louis and Pageants
  - Contains Scrapbook: Saint Louis Masque, undated (Box 128)
    Contains Scrapbook: Saint Louis Masque
  - Contains Scrapbook: Sanctuary- A Bird Masque, 1913 (Box 129)
    Contains Scrapbook: Sanctuary- A Bird Masque
  - Contains Scrapbook: Sappho and Phaon I, 1907 (Box 130)
    Contains Scrapbook: Sappho and Phaon I
  - Contains Scrapbook: Sappho and Phaon II, 1907 (Box 131)
    Contains Scrapbook: Sappho and Phaon II
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Scarecrow, 1908-1914 (Box 132)
    Contains Scrapbook: The Scarecrow
  - Contains Scrapbook: The Scarecrow, 1915 (Box 133)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Sinbad, 1917 (Box 134)
    Contains Scrapbook: Sinbad
  - Contains Scrapbook: Souvenirs, 1910-1912 (Box 135)
    Contains Scrapbook: Souvenirs
  - Contains Scrapbook: Substitute for War, undated (Box 136)
    Contains Scrapbook: Substitute for War
  - Contains Scrapbook: Theatre Programs, 1889-1905 (Box 137)
    Contains Scrapbook: Theatre Programs
  - Contains Scrapbook: Theatre Programs, 1896-1915 (Box 138)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Theatre Programs, 1903-1915 (Box 139)
  - Contains Scrapbook: A Thousand Years Ago, undated (Box 140)
    Contains Scrapbook: A Thousand Years Ago
  - Contains Scrapbook: Tomorrow I, 1912 (Box 141)
    Contains Scrapbook: Tomorrow I
  - Contains Scrapbook: Tomorrow II, 1912 (Box 142)
    Contains Scrapbook: Tomorrow II
  - Contains Scrapbook: War, 1914 (Box 143)
    Contains Scrapbook: War
  - Contains Scrapbook: War, 1918 (Box 144)
  - Contains Scrapbook: Washington I, 1919 (Box 145)
    Contains Scrapbook: Washington I
  - Contains Scrapbook: Washington II, 1919 (Box 146)
    Contains Scrapbook: Washington II
  - Contains Scrapbook: Weathergoose Woo, undated (Box 147)
    Contains Scrapbook: Weathergoose Woo
  - Contains Scrapbook: Yankee Fantasies, 1912 (Box 148)
    Contains Scrapbook: Yankee Fantasies
  - Box: 149, 1915-1939 (Box 149)
    Box: 149
    - Leaflets Dedicated To Marion Morse MacKaye, 1939 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Percy MacKaye Portraits, undated (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Marion Morse MacKaye Portraits, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Marion Morse MacKaye and her children, undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Family Members, Possible Drawing of a Steele MacKaye Invention, undated (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Business Papers, 1922 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Personal Correspondence, photocopies, 1930's (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Personal Correspondence, photocopies, Robinson-MacKaye, 1906-1928 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documents: Checkbooks, 1922-1925 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Financial Documents: Cancelled Checks, 1915-1916 (Box 149, Folder 10)
- Marion Morse MacKaye, 1874-1939; 17
  Contains correspondence, writings and journals
  - Box: 150, 1874-1939 (Box 150)
    Box: 150
    - Correspondence: A, 1912-1914 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: B-D, 1908-1914 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: E-J, 1908-1914 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: R-Z and Ephemera, 1912-1914 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Henry Lewis Morse to Marion Morse MacKaye, 1874-1905 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Marion Morse MacKaye to Mary Medberry MacKaye, 1908-1918 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, Ephemera and Bank Statements, 1911-1928 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Medical Information: Prescriptions and Remedies, 1904-1912 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Papers Related to Cambridge Property (1680 Massachusetts Avenue), 1912 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Writings By Marion Morse MacKaye, Memorandum Leaflets, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Bound Diary-Journal Volume I, Nov 28, 1898-April 27, 1899 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Bound Diary-Journal Volume II, April 28, 1899-July 6, 1899 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Bound Diary-Journal Volume III, July 7, 1899-Feb 28, 1900 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Bound Diary-Journal Volume IV, March 15, 1900-May 8, 1903 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Diary-Journal Cover Galley Proofs, undated (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: K-Q, 1905-1927 (Box 150, Folder 4)
- Robert Keith MacKaye, 1902-1934; 18
  - Box: 151, 1902-1934 (Box 151)
    Box: 151
    - Biographical Sketch, Examination Papers, Newspaper Clipping and Poems, 1902-1923 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Robert Keith MacKaye to Arviva MacKaye, 1917 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Robert Keith MacKaye to Benton MacKaye, 1930 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Robert Keith MacKaye to and from Marion Morse MacKaye, 1911-1928 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Robert Keith MacKaye to Mary Medberrry MacKaye, 1910-1918 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Robert Keith MacKaye to Percy MacKaye, 1911-1929 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - MS Honey Holler by Robert Keith MacKaye, undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Book "Honey Holler" by Robert Keith MacKaye, 1930 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Book Reviews for Honey Holler by Robert Keith MacKaye, 1930 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Other Writing by Robert Keith MacKaye, 1924-1934 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Contains Scrapbook I, 1904-1931 (Box 152)
    Contains Scrapbook I
  - Contains Scrapbook II, 1929-1931 (Box 153)
    Contains Scrapbook II
- Arvia MacKaye, 1906-1975; 19
  Contains correspondence, photographs, negatives, clippings and ephemera
  - Box: 154, 1906-1975 (Box 154)
    Box: 154
    - Announcements, Programs and Ephemera, 1911-1932 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, Prints and Sketches, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Christy MacKaye, 1929 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Benton Mckaye, 1922-1933 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Percy and Marion MacKaye, 1906-1929 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Family, 1907-1928 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Friends, 1907-1941 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Arvia MacKaye to Publishers, 1912-1929 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Music, 1913 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Memorabilia, Writings and Ephemera, undated (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Memorabilia, Writings from Childhood and Ephemera, 1912-1928 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - MS Poetry and Publications with Published Poems, 1912-1926 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings Publicity, 1910's to 1920's (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Journal of Anthroposophy, Spring 1975 (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Prints Sculptures and Other Art, undated (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Prints Personal, undated (Box 154, Folder 16)
- Christy MacKaye, 1927-1956; 20
  Contains correspondence, writings, publications and clippings
  - Box: 155, 1927-1956 (Box 155)
    Box: 155
    - Bills, 1927 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Christy MacKaye Miscellaneous, 1930-1956 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Christy MacKaye to Percy and Marion MacKaye, 1927-1931 (Box 155, Folder 3)